Guide to the Cornell AIDS Action records,1987-1996.
Cornell AIDS Action records,1987-1996
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell AIDS Action records, 1987-1996.
51-1-2746
Cornell AIDS Action
5 cubic ft., 16 oversize folders, 30 videotapes
Subject files, printed material, videos.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Sexuality and AIDS educator (1987-1990) and Coordinator of Cornell AIDS Action (1990-1992), Sharon J. Dittman. Includes records of the CU AIDS Advisory Committee (1991-1992); training, workshop, and resource materials from Cornell AIDS Action and SAFER (Students for AIDS Facts Education and Responsibility); clippings on sexuality, religion, and other topics; also, educational videos on AIDS and sexuality.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Sexuality and AIDS educator (1987-1990) and Coordinator of Cornell AIDS Action (1990-1992), Sharon J. Dittman. Includes records of the CU AIDS Advisory Committee (1991-1992); training, workshop, and resource materials from Cornell AIDS Action and SAFER (Students for AIDS Facts Education and Responsibility); clippings on sexuality, religion, and other topics; also, educational videos on AIDS and sexuality.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell AIDS Action.; Dittman, Sharon J.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University.SAFER (Students for AIDS Facts Education and Responsibility).; Cornell University.AIDS Advisory Committee.
Subjects:
Students--Health and hygiene.; AIDS (Disease)--Prevention.; AIDS (Disease)--Study and teaching.; Sex instruction.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
Related Collection: Cornell Biology and Society 451, "AIDS and Society," scrapbooks, #21-44-3298.
Series I. Annual Reports
Box 1
Series II. AIDS and Society (B+S451) Class Materials
Box 1
Series III. Training/Workshop Materials
Boxes 1-3
Series IV. Subject Files
Boxes 2-4
Series V. Media
Videos
Tape Recordings
Series VI. Posters
Boxes 5-6, oversize folders
United States
International
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Annual Reports
  - Annual Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
- Series II. AIDS and Society (B+S451) Class Materials
  - Course notes, lecture notes, copies of articles, etc., Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5-10)
  - I Think Mr. Jingles Has AIDS!, children's book by students, Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Class notebook, Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
  - Class notebook #2, Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Class notebook, Spring 1992 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
  - A Reader's Guide to AIDS Literature, book reviews by members of BS451, Spring 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Class notebook, Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Class notebook, Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Series III. Training/Workshop Materials
  - SAFER handouts (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Sexuality workshop outlines, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Scenarios (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - SAFER workshop ideas (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - SAFER sex workshop materials (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - SAFER training, Spring 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - SAFER training, Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - SAFER facilitator's manual, Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - SAFER materials, Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Flyers, posters, etc. mainly on miscellaneous trainings (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - SAFER training materials, Spring 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SAFER materials, Spring 1990? (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "Aquaintance Rape and Sexual Assault Prevention Training Manual", by Andrea Parrot (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SAFER training, Spring 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Peer Sexuality Educator's Training, Fall 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Peer Sexuality Training, Spring 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University's Male Sexuality Peer Education Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - RA training materials (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - SAFER Peer Education Program Facilitator's Manual (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sexuality Peer Education Program Facilitator's Manual (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sexuality Facilitator's Manual, Fall 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous brochures on safer sex and AIDS (reading material for SAFER facilitators) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - AIDS posters (materials for SAFER facilitators) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Peer AIDS Education Program Materials, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Peer Sexuality Education Program Materials, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - SAFER logo (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Old SAFER documents (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - SAFER training originals (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - AIDS Awareness ad in Daily Sun (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Series IV. Subject Files
  - AIDS in the Workplace: Resource Materials, including information and policy from Potsdam College (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - AIDS advisory committee-history (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Feedback/needs assessment (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Staff/faculty meeting, 1991 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Staff who work with students, 1991 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Policy (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Executive committee (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - HIV/AIDS information and resource list (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Intervention & training (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Staff/faculty education (AIDS Advisory Committee) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Education Committee (AIDS Advisory Committee) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Student education (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - "Talking with Kids About AIDS: A Resource Manual" (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Senior Honors Thesis (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Determinants of Risk-Reduction Behavioral Change in Regard to AIDS Among Cornell University Undergraduate Students, thesis by Terry Rubinstein
  - Sex and religion (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - "Common Sense About AIDS: The Patient Education Resource" (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Programs (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Resource guide for the Cornell Community (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - AIDS articles: medical (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Science, 1988 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - AIDS articles: human experience (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
  - HIV epidemiology (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Drama/theater (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - AIDS in Africa (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - AIDS in Africa, New York Times, 9/16/90-9/19/90 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - AIDS teleconference, 1989 November (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - AIDS teleconference, 1992 February 25 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Christina Lewis (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AIDS booklet (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Safe sex/AIDS pamphlets, brochures, etc. (Box 3, Folder 3-7)
  - Packet of safe sex information given out at a Gay/Lesbian picnic (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - e/sa, the other side, Christian magazines with homosexual themes (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Abstinence (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Advertising AIDS: Poster exhibit (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Advertising AIDS: Poster exhibit (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Advertising AIDS: Slide presentation HSS441 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Africa and AIDS (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - AIDSwork of Tompkins County (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Archival AIDS material (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Articles on HIV/AIDS (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - CDC HIV/AIDS Surveillance Monthly Update (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
  - Children and AIDS (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - College students and AIDS (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Condoms (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Cornell University policy statement on AIDS, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Death and dying (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Death and dying-memorial services (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Drugs and AIDS: Intravenous drug users (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Education (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Epidemiology and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Female condom (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Gay men and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Heterosexuals and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - History of AIDS/HIV (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - HIV/AIDS and mental health (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - HIV antibody test counseling (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - HIV testing, AIDS/HIV policy (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - HIV testing at Gannett (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Homophobia and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - International issues (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Latinos and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Legal issues and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lesbians and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Living with AIDS (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Media and HIV/AIDS (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Medical transmission (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Medical transmission-Kimberly Bergalis (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Names Poject-AIDS Quilt and World AIDS Day at Cornell materials (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Native Americans (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - New York State and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - New York State HIV confidentiality law (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Origin of HIV/AIDS (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Origin of HIV/AIDS: AIDS as Genocide (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - People of color and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - People of color and AIDS: African-Americans and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Perinatal transmission (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Policy issues and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Safer sex (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Safer sex: HIV transmission (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Safer sex: Oral sex (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Safer Sex Strategies workbook (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Sexuality education in schools (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - STDs (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Studies on HIV/AIDS and college students (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - TB (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Teenagers and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Transmission of HIV (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Treatments for AIDS (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Treatments for AIDS: Disease management (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Treatments for AIDS: Vaccines (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Women and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Workplace issues and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Workplace issues and AIDS: Staff brochure (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - "The AIDS Education Game" roll-up board, directions, etc. (Box 5)
- Series V. Media
  - Videos
    - Something to Live For: Allison Gertz Story, V-305
    - AIDS Bar Talk, V-306
    - Teach For America and In the Shaodw Of Love- Teen AIDS(?), V-307
    - A. Parrot, Reel 1, V-308
    - A. Parrot, Reel 2, V-309
    - AIDS, You, & Me, V-310
    - AIDS Quarterly, V-311
    - AIDS: Can I Get It?, V-312
    - AIDS: Conflicts & Choices, V-313
    - National AIDS Awareness Test, V-314
    - AIDS and Its Implication for College Campus, V-315
    - Se Met Ko, V-316
    - Discovery Journal: A Time of AIDS, V-317
    - AIDS Awareness Celebrity Show, V-318
    - Questions and Responses about AIDS/HIV, V-319
    - Health Beat, Eva Obarzanak, Dave Levitzsky, 1984, V-320
    - AIDS: Everything with Surgeon General, V-321
    - Joan's Story, V-322
    - Facing AIDS: Teens ask a young man what it's like, V-323
    - Eddie's Story, V-324
    - Eddie's Story, V-325; (copy 2)
    - Sex, Drugs, and HIV, V-326
    - AIDS: Changing the Rules, V-327
    - AIDS Alert, V-328
    - AIDS: Why Should I Care?, V-329
    - Teen AIDS in Focus, V-330
    - AIDS PSA, V-331
    - AIDS Video Journal: New Therapies for HIV Infection, V-332
    - Everybody's at Risk, V-333
    - A Time to Talk: Sex and AIDS in the 90's from a Student Perspective, V-707, V-10708 (Box 7)
  - Tape Recordings
    - AIDS Music, TR-7351a
    - AIDS - Gay and Lesbian Concerns, April 15, 1987; TR-7352a
    - Women and HIV Infection, 1991; TR-7353a
    - New Ways Ministry presents: Growing Up Gay and Catholic, TR-7354a-7355a
    - Addressing Student Sexuality, TR-7356a
    - Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Health Education, TR-7357a & 7359a
    - HIV in the '90s: Campus and Community, TR-7358a
- Series VI. Posters
  - United States
    - Alabama
      - Alabama Department of Public Health, "Don't Die With AIDS, Live With Facts", 1987 (Folder 1)
      - Alabama Department of Public Health AIDS Prevention Program, "He Has His Daddy's Smile And His Mother's AIDS", 1988 (Folder 1)
      - Alabama Department of Public Health AIDS Prevention Program, "He wouldn't give up shooting up... so I gave him up", 1989 (Folder 1)
      - Alabama Department of Public Health AIDS Prevention Program, "I Didn't Know I Had AIDS... Not Until My Baby Was Born With It", 1989 (Folder 1)
      - Alabama Department of Public Health AIDS Prevention Program, What's Your Chance of Getting AIDS Tonight?", 1989 (Folder 1)
      - Alabama Department of Public Health AIDS Prevention Program, "You CANNOT get AIDS from...", 1988 (Folder 1)
    - American Red Cross-HIV/AIDS Program
      - Posters with proverbs from Ethiopia, Guinea, Cameroon, Ghana, and Sierra Leone (Folder 15)
    - Arizona
      - Maricopa Area Health Education Center, "The Positive Woman" (Folder 1)
    - California
      - Asian AIDS Project, "It's Natural" (Folder 1)
      - CDC, displayed at Stanford, "Don't just worry about HIV..." (Folder 1)
      - CDC, displayed at Stanford, "This is the way many people deal with HIV." (Folder 1)
      - Department of Public Health, City and County of San Francisco, "AIDS: Phòng Benh Hon Chua Benh..." (in Vietnamese), 1988 (Folder 1)
      - Kampanya Ng Edukasyon..., "Isang mensahe sa bawa't Pilipino sa Amerika." (in Tagalog) (Folder 1)
      - Kimono Condoms, "Wrap your man in pleasure: Kimono Condoms" (Folder 1)
      - Kimono Condoms, "...you remember buying the beer, setting the alarm, and getting the condom..." (Folder 1)
      - Korean Community Service Center, "Remember... Any Race Can Get Aids" (in English and Korean) (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "Be A Rubberman- Use A Condom Every Time (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "Be Here for the Cure" [2 copies] (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "Dress for the occasion.", 1988 (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "Get Carried Away With Condoms", 1990 (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "Life Liberty and the Pursuit of Happiness" (Folder 1)
      - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, "The moral majority... Family values... Right to life" (Folder 1)
    - Centers for Disease Control
      - "1800-AIDS-TTY" (Folder 3)
      - "AIDS is a problem for Hispanics, too." (one in English, one in Spanish) (Folder 3)
      - "A message to the third man in my life." (Folder 3)
      - "Ayudando una persona que tiene SIDA" (in Spanish) (Folder 3)
      - "A man who shoots up can be very giving." (Folder 3)
      - "¿Cómo se adquiere el SIDA?" (in Spanish) (Folder 3)
      - "Do You Talk About AIDS On The First Date?" (Folder 3)
      - "El licor, el crack y otras drogas..." (in Spanish) (Folder 3)
      - "Existe una conección entre el SIDA y las enfermedades venéreas." (in Spanish) (Folder 3)
      - "Getting high doesn't cause AIDS." [2 sizes] (Folder 3)
      - "Have You Talked With Your Wife About AIDS?" (Folder 3)
      - "Heard Much About AIDS Lately?" (Folder 3)
      - "How About Dinner, A Movie, And A Talk About AIDS?" [2 sizes] (Folder 3)
      - "How much do your children know about AIDS?" (Folder 3)
      - "How Would You Deal With It If One Of You Got AIDS?" (Folder 3)
      - "If Your Man Is Dabbling In Drugs..." (Folder 3)
      - "It might take more than motherwit to tell my children what to do about AIDS." (Folder 3)
      - "If he doesn't have a condom..." [2 versions] (Folder 3)
      - "If you get the AIDS virus now..." [2 sizes] (Folder 3)
      - "Most people think HIV is only a problem in big cities..." (Folder 3)
      - "No Matter What Shape You're In, Anyone Can Get The AIDS Virus" (Folder 3)
      - "On the wrong track" [3 sizes] (Folder 3)
      - "Putting On A Condom Is Just As Simple" (Folder 3)
      - "Sharing Needles Can Get You More Than High" (Folder 4)
      - "She shows all the signs of having HIV." [2 versions] (Folder 4)
      - "Since I got HIV..." (Folder 4)
      - "Stop Worrying About How You Won't Get AIDS...", 1993 (Folder 4)
      - "There's a simple way to prevent AIDS." (Folder 4)
      - "This is the way many people deal with HIV.", 1991 (Folder 4)
      - "Today, almost one million Americans are infected with HIV." (Folder 4)
      - "Today, people with HIV are doing something most of us didn't think possible." (Folder 4)
      - "What Have You Got Against A Condom?" (6 copies in English, 2 copies in Spanish) (Folder 4)
      - "When I found out I had HIV at age 17, I learned that anyone can get it.", 1993 (Folder 4)
      - "Why alcohol, crack and other drugs can put you at risk for the AIDS virus." (Folder 4)
      - "With AIDS around, gonorrhea, syphilis & herpes are fair warning." (Folder 4)
      - "You Won't Get AIDS From A Bug Bite." (Folder 4)
      - "You Won't Get AIDS In A Restaurant." (Folder 4)
    - Colorado
      - Colorado Department of Education, "How Well Do You Know The 63 People You Had Sex With Last Night?" (Folder 1)
      - Colorado Department of Health, "Aids Kills. Bleach Works. Use It!" [2 versions] (Folder 1)
      - Colorado Department of Health, "Agarra la Onda/Get Hip!" (Folder 1)
      - Love Life Safely, no text., 1993 (Folder 1)
    - Connecticut
      - Concilio Hispano de la Salud, "Edúcate sobre el SIDA" (in Spanish) (Folder 2)
      - Concilio Hispano de la Salud, "El SIDA es una enfermedad..." (one copy in Spanish, one in English) (Folder 2)
      - Concilio Hispano de la Salud, "Yo Tengo SIDA, Abrázame..." (in Spanish) (Folder 2)
      - State of Connecticut Department of Health Services, "I went away to school and got a bad grade... HIV+" (Folder 2)
      - State of Connecticut Department of Health Services, "Only A Fool Fools Around." (Folder 2)
      - Concerned Citizens for Humanity, Ltd., "Hurt. Anger. Fear. Loneliness." (one copy in English, one in Spanish) (Folder 2)
      - Concerned Citizens for Humanity, Ltd., "Perception: AIDS can't happen to me." (one copy in English, one in Spanish) (Folder 2)
      - Concerned Citizens for Humanity, Ltd., "Por favor. Ayude a los niños con EL SIDA." (one copy in Spanish, one in English) (Folder 2)
      - Concerned Citizens for Humanity, Ltd., "Women. Reality. HIV-AIDS." (Folder 2)
    - Florida
      - Florida AIDS Hotline, "I Have AIDS...", 1990 (Folder 2)
      - Florida International University, "What Do You Know About AIDS?" (Folder 2)
    - Georgia
      - Atlanta West Treatment Center, "Are You A Prisoner?" (Folder 2)
      - Street Team for AIDS Risk Reduction, "One Bad Needle and You're Stuck." (Folder 2)
    - Hawaii
      - AIDS Education in Hawaii Project, "World AIDS Day", 1992 (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Wise Up! No Go Ova' Board, Eh!" (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Fo' Da Last Time! You Not Goin' Get AIDS From Da Showers!" (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Getting Married? Congratulations!" (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Ioe Po O Le Leai" (in Hawaiian) (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "No Clayton! I Don't Think 'Safe Sex'..." (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Raymond! I Don't Care What Da Kids Say! SPINACH Does Not Cause AIDS!" (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Things Change Brah!..." (Folder 2)
      - Hawaii Department of Health, "Yes Or No..." (one side in English, one in Hawaiian) (Folder 2)
      - Planned Parenthood of Hawaii, "Football can be risky without protection... So can sex" (Folder 2)
    - Idaho
      - Idaho AIDS Program, "No One Can Afford To Ignore AIDS" (Folder 5)
      - Idaho STD/AIDS Program, "Raise AIDS Awareness" (Folder 5)
    - Illinois
      - The Authority of State of Illinois, "None of these will give you AIDS.", 1985 (Folder 5)
      - The Authority of the State of Illinois, "Their Past Could Make You History.", 1992 (Folder 5)
      - Illinois Department of Public Health, "AIDS Facts For Life", 1992 (Folder 5)
      - Illinois Department of Public Health, "Beware Of Fly-By-Night Relationships.", 1992 (Folder 5)
      - Illinois Department of Public Health, "Take This Test Before It's Time To Take This One", 1992 (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "All you need is LOVE" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "Bad case of Loving you..." (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "I Want Your Sex" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "New Love" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "Open Your Heart" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "She Loves You" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "So In Love" (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "Survey Says:..." (Folder 5)
      - Northern Illinois University, University Health Service, "Whats Love Got To Do With It?" (Folder 5)
    - Louisiana
      - Louisiana AIDS Prevention Project, "Don't Let AIDS Deal You A Losing Hand..." (Folder 5)
      - Union of American Congregations Committee on AIDS, "Who will say Kaddish for me?", 1989 (Folder 5)
    - Maryland
      - Health Education Resource Organization (HERO), "AIDS Can Blow Your High.", 1987 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "AIDS in the Black Community" (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Before You Leave, Ask The Bartender For A Nightcap.", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Condomplation" (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Don't Let The Bed Bugs Bite", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "First Love? Not Quite.", 1991 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Good Things Come In Condoms", 1991 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "How To Avoid AIDS: A Few Tips.", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "If You Prick Your Arm, Arm Your Prick.", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Keep It In Your Pants", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Sleep With A Lifeguard Tonight.", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "Smart Sportswear For The Active Man.", 1993 (Folder 6)
      - HERO, "There Are A Lot Of Things Worth Protecting..." [2 different versions], 1990 (Folder 6)
      - Maryland AIDS Hotline, "He Loves Me. He Loves Me Not." (Folder 6)
      - Maryland AIDS Hotline, "How To Keep From Getting Lovesick" [2 versions] (Folder 6)
      - Maryland AIDS Hotline, In 1984, We Discovered The AIDS Virus. In 1850, We Discovered A Way To Stop It." (Folder 6)
      - Maryland AIDS Hotline, "Last Night, This Woman Slept With Every One Of Her Boyfriend's Ex-Lovers." (Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts
      - Massachusetts Department of Public Health, "Prevent AIDS... Use One" (Folder 6)
      - Massachusetts Department of Public Health, "Take Care. Don't Share. AIDS Kills" (Folder 6)
    - Michigan
      - Michigan Department of Public Health, "Everybody's Doing It..." (Folder 6)
      - Michigan Department of Public Health, "Take The HIV Test..." (Folder 6)
      - Michigan Department of Public Health, "Unlike True Love AIDS Is Forever" (Folder 6)
      - Michigan Department of Public Health, "Winners Always Use Condoms" (Folder 6)
    - Minnesota
      - American Indian Health Care Association, "AIDS Is Not A Quick Kill" (Folder 6)
      - American Indian Health Care Association, "Let the light of our teachings guide the way to healthy behavior.", 1990 (Folder 6)
      - American Indian Health Care Association, "You Can't Get AIDS By..." (Folder 6)
      - Minneapolis Health Department, "AIDS Is NOT Spread By:" (Folder 6)
    - Mississippi
      - Mississippi State Department of Health, "Is Your Lover Handing You A Death Sentence?" (Folder 6)
    - Missouri
      - Missouri Department of Health, "AIDS Is Scary, But A Zit Is Real. Right?" (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "El no dejó de inyectarse drogas..." (in Spanish) (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "Heard Much About AIDS Lately?" (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "He wouldn't give up shooting up...so I gave him up." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "If You Cheat On Your Partner..." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "If You're Dabbling In Drugs..." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "If Your Man Is Dabbling In Drugs..." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "I Love Sex." (Folder 6)
      - Missouri Department of Health, "No Matter What Shape You're In..." (Folder 6)